A Guide to the David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1997-2000, RG 49 FA1506
Rockefeller Archive Center
- David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1997-2000, 49; 27.14 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes, 1 record storage box.
  - Religion, 1997-2000; 23; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Religion - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 4-5)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Interfaith Alliance Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Tanenbaum Center for Interreligious Understanding, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      Formerly the Rabbi Marc H. Tannenbaum Foundation.
    - Churches - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
    - Churches - The Cathedral Church of St. John The Divine, 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Churches - Friends of Dresden, Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Churches - Reims Cathedral, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Churches - Riverside Church, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Churches - Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Missions - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Maine Sea Coast Missionary Society, Salvation Army (in memory of William S. Ogden), Salvation Army of Greater New York.
    - Missions - New York City Mission Society, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Missions - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF), 1997-2000; 24; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - RBF - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Family Office, 1997-2000; 25; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller and Company, Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1997-2000; 26; 6.08 Cubic Feet 16 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller, David - A-Al, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 10-11)
    - Rockefeller, David - Am-Bl, 1997-2000 (Box 50, Folder 1-8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Bm-Co, 1997-2000 (Box 51, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Cp-Ek, 1997-2000 (Box 52, Folder 1-8)
    - Rockefeller, David - El-F, 1997-2000 (Box 53, Folder 1-8)
    - Rockefeller, David - G-Ha, 1997-2000 (Box 54, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Ha-Ke, 1997-2000 (Box 55, Folder 1-7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Kf-Lh, 1997-2000 (Box 56, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Li-Mi, 1997-2000 (Box 57, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Mj-O, 1997-2000 (Box 58, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - P-Rj, 1997-2000 (Box 59, Folder 1-10)
    - Rockefeller, David - Rl-Se, 1997-2000 (Box 60, Folder 1-7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Sf-T, 1997-2000 (Box 61, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - U-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 62, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks-Statements - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      Duncan Phillips Award Dinner, Washington D.C., November 2, 2000. Economic Club of New York.
    - Rockefeller, David - Autograph-Photograph Requests, 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 2-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
      Business Committee for the Arts. French Legion of Honor. Grand Croix of the Legion d'Honneur. Japan. Marquis Who's Who Publication Board. Mexican Order of the Aztec Eagle. Parks and Preservation Award. Thailand.
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - Medal of Freedom, 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Beetles - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Birthdays, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      Nelson Mandela Breakfast
    - Rockefeller, David - Interviews - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      Forbes Magazine, History Channel, International Communication Network, and others.
    - Rockefeller, David - Investments - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Personal Services - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Seal Harbor - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden, Seal Harbor Water Company.
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      Brazil (Rio de Janeiro), Dominican Republic, Panama and Costa Rica, Japan, Mexico, Morocco, San Francisco, Spain.
    - Rockefeller, David - Works of Art - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, Peggy - Death - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller Family - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller, John D. - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      Lakeview Cemetery Foundation
    - Rockefeller, Rodman C. (Letters of Condolences), 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      Condolences
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1997-2000; 27; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Rockefeller Foundation - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University, 1997-2000; 28; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller University - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      Fisher Center for Alzheimer's Research, Peggy Rockefeller Concerts.
    - Rockefeller University - Rockefeller Archive Center (RAC), 1997-2000 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller University - Rockefeller Archive Center (RAC) - Governing Council Meetings, 1997-1999 (Box 65, Folder 4-5, Box 66, Folder 1)
  - S-W, 1997-2000; 29; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Science - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, History of Science Society, National Academy of Sciences, New York Hall of Science.
    - Science - New York Academy of Sciences, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      Bar Harbor Fire Department, Downeast Horizons, Island Foundation, Northeast Harbor Fire Company, Otter Creek Fire Company, Seal Harbor Fire Company, Seal Harbor Village Improvement Society, Somersville Fire Company.
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Westchester Organizations - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      Columbia County Annual Giving, Hilltop Engine Co., North Tarrytown's Volunteer Fire Department and Exempt Benevolent Association.
    - Winrock International - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Welfare, 1997-2000; 30; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Welfare - A-K, 1997-2000 (Box 66, Folder 9-10)
    - Welfare - L-R, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Welfare - S-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Concern Worldwide, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Visiting Nurse Service of New York, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Animals - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      Animal Medical Center
    - Blind - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      American Foundation for the Blind, The Eye-Bank for Sight Restoration, Foundation Fighting Blindness, Hawkness Eye Institute, Massachusetts Eye and Ear Infirmary, ORBIS International, Surgical Eye Expeditions.
    - Community Centers - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      Catholic Community Services, East Side House Settlement, Henry Street Settlement, Lenox Hill Neighborhood House, Union Settlement Association.
    - Community Centers - University Settlement Society of New York, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Day Nurseries - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      Children First, Inc., Kids Corner Community Child Care, Elizabeth Mascia Child Care Center, Mt. Desert Nursery School
    - Family Counseling - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      Family Service of Westchester, Public Conversations Project.
    - Handicapped - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
    - Handicapped - The Dole Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Homes - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      Bethel Homes
    - Housing - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      Association for Neighborhood and Housing Development, Inc., Phipps Community Development Corporation, Settlement Housing Fund.
    - Legal - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      Legal Aid Society
    - United Funds - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      United Way of Columbia County, United Way of Eastern Maine, United Way of Greater Portland, United Way of New York City, United Way of the Tarrytowns, United Way of Westchester and Putnam.
  - Women, 1997-2000; 31; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Women - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      Global Fund for Women, International Women's Health Coalition, Lithuanian Women's Federation, Ms. Foundation for Women, National Coalition of 100 Black Women, National Partnership for Women and Families, National Women's Law Center, New York Women's Foundation, Society for Women's Health Research, Women's Legal Defense Fund.
    - National Coalition of 100 Black Women, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Now Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Youth, 1997-2000; 32; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - Youth - A-F, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
      92nd Street Y, A Better Chance, Abnaki Girl Scout Council, Boy Scouts of America, Boys and Girls Club of Northern Westchester, Boys Club of New York, Children's Advocacy Center of Manhattan, Child Care Action Campaign, Children's Defense Fund, Citizen's Committee for Children, Downeast Family YMCA, Fund for Cooperative Initiatives, Inc.
    - Youth - G-M, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
      Girls, Inc., Girl Scouts of Westchester-Putnam, Green Chimney's Children's Services, Jobs for Youth, Kaiser Youth Foundation, Kids First for America, Lives Under Construction Boy's Ranch, Madison Area YMCA, Madison Square Boys and Girls Club, Mt. Desert Island YMCA.
    - Youth - N-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
      National Youth Advocacy Coalition, New Yorkers for Children, North Country Treetops, One to One, Partnership with Children, Police Athletic League, Jackie Robinson Foundation, Tarrytown-North Tarrytown Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), Tarrytown YMCA, Think Quest 2000, Young People's Leadership Foundation, Youth Development Foundation, Inc., Youth Forum, Inc., Youth for Understanding, Youth in Distress in Israel, YMCA-YWCA Camping Services, Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA).
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of America, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Greater New York Councils, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - Covenant House, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - Girl Scouts Council of Greater New York, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - The Children's Aid Society, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - Hugh O'Brien Youth Foundation (HOBY), 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - Save the Children, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - Vocational Foundation, Inc. Island Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - Camps - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
      Greenwood Music Camp.
    - Camps - Boys Harbor, Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 25)
    - Camps - The Fresh Air Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 25)